import { Quiz } from '../../types';

const GenitiveTranslationQuiz: Quiz[] = [
  {
    description: 'Bez koho, čeho?',
    name: 'Genitive',
    questions: [
      {
        answer: ['around'],
        question: 'okolo'
      },
      {
        answer: ['into', 'to'],
        question: 'do'
      },
      {
        answer: ['without'],
        question: 'bez'
      },
      {
        answer: ['except'],
        question: 'kromě'
      },
      {
        answer: ['instead of'],
        question: 'místo'
      },
      {
        answer: ['from'],
        question: 'od'
      },
      {
        answer: ['next to', 'beside'],
        question: 'vedle'
      },
      {
        answer: ['according to', 'based on'],
        question: 'podle'
      },
      {
        answer: ['at'],
        question: 'u'
      },
      {
        answer: ['from'],
        question: 'z'
      },
      {
        answer: ['during'],
        question: 'během'
      },
      {
        answer: ['in the middle', 'middle'],
        question: 'uprostřed'
      }
    ]
  }
];

export default GenitiveTranslationQuiz;
